Inventory of the Great Britain, Foreign Office, Wellington House publications
Hoover Institution Archives
- Grey, Edward (Sir). "Speech... 22 March, 1915." Darling, London, 1915, 14 pp. (Box 5)
- Grice, J. Watson. "The Resource of the Empire." International Information Section, Vol I. George Allen & Unwin, London, 1917, 64 pp. (Box 5)
- Gwatkin, H. M. "Britain's Case Against Germany. A Letter to a Neutral." Reprinted from the Nation, October, 14th, 1916. T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 15 pp. (Box 5)
- Haig, Douglas. "Report: London Gazette" (Box 6)
- Hall, Moedaunt. "Some Naval Yarns." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917. 83 pp. (Box 6)
- "Hands Across the Sea. Speeches by Walter Hines Page, A. J. Balfour, Joseph H. Choate, Viscount Bryce..." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 24 pp. (Box 6)
- Hanson, C. A. "London v. Germany. The War Effort of the Capital." W. H. Smith, London, 11 pp. (Box 6)
- Hard, William. "How the English Take the War." Reprinted from The Metropolitan. Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917. 30 pp. (Box 6)
- Headlam, J.W. "The Dead Lands of Europe." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917. 36 pp. (Box 6)
- Headlam, James Wycliffe. "England, Germany and Europe." Reprinted from the Church Quarterly Review. Macmillan, London, 1914, 24 pp. (Box 6)
- Headlam, J.W. "The Issue". Constable, London, 1917. 157 pp. (Box 14)
- Headlam, Ja.W. "The Truth about England Exposed to in a Letter to a Neutral." Thomas Nelson, London, 1915. 18 pp. (Box 6)
- Henderson, Arthur. "The League of Nations and Labour." Oxford University Press, London, 1918, 13 pp. (Box 6)
- Heuvel, J. Van Den. "Slave Raids in Belgium" (Box 6)
- Hope, Anthony. "Militarism: German and British." Darling, London, 1915, 6 pp. (Box 6)
- Hope, Anthony. "Why Italy is with Allies." Richard Clay, London. 1917. 16 pp. (Box 6)
- "The Horrors of Louvain. By an Eye-witness." "Sunday Times", London. 52 pp. (Box 6)
- "The Horror of Wittenberg." Official Report to the British Government. C. Arthur Pearson, London, 1916. 32 pp. 2d Edition. (Box 6)
- "How Goes the War. A Soldier's Answer." Darling, London, 11 pp. (Box 6)
- Hurd, Archibald. "The Defences of the Empire." International Information Series, British Empire Section, Vol. II, George Allen & Unwin, London. 1917. 64 pp. (Box 6)
- "Hungary and the War." Reprinted from The Times. Darling, London, 1915, 14 pp. (Box 6)
- Howard, Keble. "The Quality of Mercy. How British Prisoners of War Were Taken to Germany in 1914." Avenue Press, London. 1918. 15 pp. (Box 6)
- Hurd, Archibald. "Germany Besieged. Memories of 1870-1871." Chapman & Hall, London. Reprinted from The Fortnightly Review, August, 1916. 13 pp. (Box 6)
- Hurd, Archibald. "Outlawry at Sea. An Indictment of the German Navy." Chapman & Hall, London, 15 pp. (Box 6)
- Hurd, Archibald. "A Sure Shield." Jas. Truscott, London, 14 pp. (Box 6)
- Hurd, Percy. "Canada, Past, Present and Future." International Information Series. British Empire Section. Vol. V. George Allen & Unwin, London, 1918, 64 p. (Box 6)
- Hyamson, Albert M. "Great Britain and the Jews." Edinburgh Press, London, 1918, 12 pp. (Box 6)
- Hymans, M. Asquith, H. H. Standaert, M. "Fete Nationale Belge. Belgian Independence Day. Belgische Onafhankelykheidsdag...Addresses delivered at the Royal Albert Hall,..." July 21st, 1916. 64 pp.(In French, English and Flemish) (Box 6)
- "Independence Day in London, 1918." Resolutions and speeches at the Central Hall, Westminster. Hodder & Stoughton, London, 34 pp. (Box 6)
- "Is Germany Anti-Catholic?" By a Catholic. Burns & Oates, London, 30 pp. (Box 6)
- "Issue of the War-No.2." Romania. Sept. 1918, 4 pp. (Box 6)
- "Jews Among the Entente Leaders." R. Clay, London, 1918, 35 pp. (Box 6)
- Joergensen, Johannes. "False Witness. Authorized Translation of 'Klokke Roland'." Hodder & Stoughton, London. 1916. 227 p. (Box 14)
- Johannet, Rene (editor). "Pan-Germanism Versus Christendom." Hodder & Stoughton, London. 1916. 184 p. (Box 14)
- Jonesco, Take. "The Policy of National Instinct." Sir Joseph Causton, London. 1916. 108 pp. (Box 6)
- Keating, J. "The Freedom of the Seas." Reprinted from The Month, March, 1917, 16 pp. (Box 6)
- "The King at the Front. Official Photographs in Colours." Daily Mail, London. 16 plates. (Box 6)
- Koch, Theodore Wesley. "University of Louvain and its Library." J. M. Dent, London, 1917, 28 pp. (Box 6)
- "A Kruff's Director on German Policy." Beacon No.6. 4 pp. (Box 6)
- Langenhove, Fernand van. "The Growth of a Legend." Putnam, London. 1916. (Box 15)
- Lavisse, E. Andler, Ch. "German Theory and Practice of War. Studies and Documents on the War." Lib. Armand Colin, Paris. 1915. 48 pp. (Box 7)
- Law, Hugh A. "Why is Ireland at War?." Maunstel, London. 1916. 42 pp. (Box 7)
- Lawson, John A. "Memories of Delville Wood. South Africa's Great Battle." T. Maskew Miller, Cape Town. 1918. 16 pp. (Box 7)
- League of Neutral States. "A Statement from the Dutch Section." Hayman, Christy & Lilly, London. 2 pp. (Box 7)
- "The Legend of the 'Frances-Tireurs' Warfare in Belgium." As set forth in the German pamphlet "Der Franktiereurkrieg in Belgien: Gestaendnisse der belgischen Presse." Extract from note 118 of the Bureau Documentaire Belge. Truscott, London, 1916, 40 pp. (Box 7)
- Lewin, Evans. "The Commonwealth of Australia International Information Services." British Empire Sections, Vol. III. George Allen & Unwin, London, 1917, 64 pp. (Box 7)
- Lewin, Evans. "German Rule in Africa." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1918. 48 pp. (Box 7)
- Lichtervelde, Louis de (Count). "August the Fourth, 1914, in the Belgian Parliament." Wightman, London, 1918, 37 pp. (Box 7)
- "A List of Neutral Ships Sunk by the Germans, from August 8th, 1914, to April 26th, 1917." Alabaster, Passmore, London, 40 pp. (Box 7)
- Lloyd-George, David. "British War Aims. Statement..." Janurary 5, 1918. Hazell, Watson & Viney, 12 pp. (Box 7)
- Lloyd-George, David. "The Great War. Speech..." Sept 19th, 1914. Harrison, London, 14 pp. (Box 7)
- Loti, Pierre. "The Trial of the Barbarians; being 'l'Outrage des barbares'". Longmans, Green, London, 1917. 21 pp. (Box 7)
- Loyal India. "An Interview with Lord Hardinge of Penshurst by a London Correspondent of the New York Times." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 15 pp. (Box 7)
- Loyson, Paul Hyacinthe. "The Gods in the Battle." A reply to "Above the Battle." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 290 pp. (Box 15)
- Lynch, Arthur. "The Applied Cause is Ireland's Hope." 4 pp. Alabaster Passmore, London. (Box 7)
- Mackenzie, Dewitt. "The Awakening of India." Hodder & Stoughton, London. 1917. 159 p. (Box 7)
- Mckenzie, F. A. "Americans at the Front." Hodder & Stoughton, london, 1917. 33 p. (Box 7)
- Mc Kenzie, F. A. "British Railways and the War." Menpes, London, 1917, 32 pp. (Box 7)
- McKenzie, F. A. "Serving the King's Men." Hodder & Stoughton, London. 1918. 74 pp. (Box 7)
- Maclean, Frank. "Germany's Colonial Failure." Burrup, Mathieson, & Spra gue, London, 1918, 22 pp. (Box 7)
- "The Mails as a German War Weapon. Memorandum on the Censorship of Mails Carried by Neutral Ships." Eyre & Spottiswoode, London. 1916. 24 pp. (Box 7)
- Map. "Northern France Sector." Albert. Stanford's Geog. Estab., London. (Box 7)
- Marcosson, Isaac F. "A Visit to Sir Douglas Haig." Reprinted from Everybody's Magazine. Avenue Press, London, 1917. 31 pp. (Box 7)
- Massey, W. T. "The Desert Campaigns." Constavle, London, 1918, 178 pp. Illustrated by James McBey. (Box 15)
- Masterman, E. W. G. "The Deliverance of Jerusalem." Hodder & Stoughton, London. 1918. 51 p. (Box 7)
- Mathews, Basil, ed. "Christ and the World at War; Sermons Preached in War-time." Edited, with an introduction, by Basil Mathews. James Clarke & Co. London. 1917. 191 p. (Box 7)
- Mathews, Basil. "The Freedom of Jerusalem." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1918. 22 pp. (Box 7)
- Mathews, Basil. "The Vista of Victory." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 16 pp. (Box 7)
- Maude, F.S. "Report: London Gazette" (Box 7)
- Melgar, Francisco. "A Spanish Catholic's Visit to England. Impressions..." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 56 pp. (Box 8)
- "Memorandum of the Belgian Government on the Deportation and Forced Labour of the Belgian Ccivil Population Ordered by the German Government." Barber, London, 29 pp. Le Havre, Feb. 1, 1917. (Box 8)
- "The Men who Tidy Uup. By One who has Served in a British Labour Battalion." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917. 15 pp. (Box 8)
- Mercier, D. J. (Cardinal). "Courge, My Brother! A Pastoral Letter by Cardinal Mercier. Lent, 1917." Burns & Oates, London, 20 pp. (Box 8)
- Mercier, D. J. (Cardinal). "For those in Captivity. A Sermon Preached... 26 November..." Burrup, Mathieson, & Sprague, London. 1917, 8 pp. (Box 8)
- Mercier, D. J. (Cardinal). "My Return from Rome. Pastoral Letter, Lent, 1916." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 19 pp. (Box 8)
- Mercier, D. J. (Cardinal). "The Seizure of Church Bells and Organs in Occupied Belgium." Campfield Press, St. Albans, 1918, 8 pp. (Box 8)
- Mercier, D. J. (Cardinal). "The Voice of Belgium." Burns & Oates, London. 230 p. (Box 15)
- Mercier, D. J. (Cardinal). "The Voice of God. A Pastoral Letter." Burrup, Mathieson & Sprague, London, 1916, 30 pp. (Box 8)
- "Microbe-Culture at Bukarest. Discoveries at the German Legation." From the Romanian Official Documents. Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 16 pp. (Box 8)
- Millet, Philippe. "Comrades in Arms. What the French Army Really Thinks of the British." Hodder & Stoughton, 1916. 252 pp. (Box 15)
- Mills, J. Saxon. "Britain's Financial Burden." Eyre & Spottiswoode, London, 2 pp. (Box 8)
- "The Ministry of Healing. Britain's Care of the Wounded." Petty & Sons, London, 24 pp. Pictorial. (Box 8)
- Mitrany, D. "Great Rumania. A Study in National Ideals." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 20 pp. (Box 8)
- Mittel-Afrika. "The Black Empire of Germany's Dreams." The Beacon, No.8. (Box 8)
- Mokveld, L. "The German Fury in Belgium." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917. 247 p. (Box 15)
- Montague, C. E. "The Front Line. With Drawings by Muirhead Bone." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 12 pp. (Box 8)
- Montague, C. E. "Notes from Calais Base and Pictures of its Many Activities." T. Fisher. Unwin, London, 1918, 48 pp. (Box 8)
- "More Contemptibles." Dield & Queen, London, 4 pp. (Box 8)
- Morgan, J. H. "A Dishonoured Army. German Atrocities in France with Unpublished Records." Spottiswoode, London, 1915, 20 pp. Reprinted from the Nineteenth Century, June, 1915. (Box 8)
- Muehlon, Wilhelm. "Diary. Notes Written Early in the War." Cassell & Co. London. 1918. 247 p. (Box 17)
- Mugerditchian, Esther (Mrs.) "From Turkish Toils. The narrative of an Armenian Family's escape." C. Arthur Pearson, London, 1918, 51 pp. (Box 8)
- "Murder Again!" Causton, London, 1 pp. (Box 8)
- "The Murder of Captain Fryatt." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1916, 47 pp. (Box 8)
- Murray, Gilbert. "Ethical Problems of the War." Reprinted from The Inquirer of 10 Oct. 1915. Thomas Nelson, London, 24 pp. (Box 8)
- Murray, Gilbert. "Faith, War, and Policy." Houghton Middlin, N.Y. Oxford University Press, England. 1918, 280 pp. (Box 15)
- Murray, Gilbert. "Impressions of Scandinavia in War Time." Reprinted from the Westminster Gazette. T. Fisher Unwin, London, 32 pp. (Box 8)
- Murray, Gilbert. "The League of Nations and the Democratic Idea." Oxford University Press, 1918, 30 pp. (Box 8)
- Nash, Paul (Artist). "British Artists at the Front. Part Three. Continuation of 'The Western Front'." Country Life, London, 15 plates. (Box 9)
- "A National Home for the Jewish People. The British Government's recognition of the Zionist movement." Reprinted from Jewish Chronicle, R. Clay & Sons, London, 1917, 16 pp. (Box 9)
- "Necessity Knows No Law." The Beacon No.4. Leaflet, R. Clay, London. (Box 9)
- Nevinson, C.R.W. "The Roads of France." Hudson & Kearns, London, 6 pp. (Box 9)
- The NEW German Empire. "A Study of German War Aims from German Sources." Reprinted from the Round Table for March, 1917. Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 32 pp. (Box 9)
- Newbolt, Henry (Sir). "A Note on the History of Submarine War." Longmans, Green, London, 1918, 27 pp. (Box 9)
- Newbolt, Henry. "The War and the Nations." Reprinted from the Fortnightly Review. August, 1915. R. Clay, London, 1915, 12 pp. (Box 9)
- Nippold, Otfried. "The Awakening of the German People." George Aleen & Unwin, London, 1918, 60 pp. (Box 9)
- Nippold, Otfried."Dangerous Optimism." George Allen & Unwin, London, 1918, 20 pp. (Box 9)
- "No Small Stir. What the Pope Really Said About the Great War, by 'Diplomaticus'" Society of SS. Peter and Paul, London, 1917, 40 pp. (Box 9)
- "Norway's Shipping Losses During the War, to the End of June, 1917. Translated and Summarised from 'Sjoeforklaringer over Norske Skibes Krigsforlis' (Nautical Declarations regarding the War losses of Norwegian Shipping)." Avenue Press, London. 1918. 28 pp. (Box 9)
- Nothomb, Pedro. "Belgica Martir" (Box 9)
- Nyrop, Christophe. "France." Heinemann, London, 1917, 125 pp. (Box 15)
- O'Connor, T. P. "Address,... to the President of the French Republic...30th April, 1915." Darling, London, 1915, 8 pp. (Box 9)
- O' Neill, H.C. "The Military Outlook. The Allies' Prospects of Victory." George Allen & Unwin, London, 1918, 23 pp. (Box 9)
- O'Neill, H.C. "A History of the British Navy During the War." Adapted from Colonel John Buchan's "History of the War." Thomas Nelson, London, 1918, 360 pp. (Box 17)
- "The Ottoman Domination." Reprinted from the Round Table. T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 18 pp. (Box 9)
- Page, Walter Hines. Bryce, Viscount. Cecil, Robert (Lord) et al. "Companionship in Arms. Speeches... April 12, 1917." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 24 pp. (Box 9)
- "Pan-German Peace Fantasies." Manpes, London. 4 pp. (Box 9)
- "Pan-German Versus Christendom. The Conversion of a Neutral, Open Letter by M. Emile Pruem." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1916. 184 pp. (Box 9)
- "Parliaments Vote of Thanks to the Forces" (Box 9)
- Parker, Gilbert. "Is England Apathetic?" (Box 9)
- Parker, Gilbert. "Letters" (Box 9)
- Passelecq, Fernand. "BelgianUunity and the Flemish Movement." Reprinted from The Nineteenth Century and After, October, 1916. Spottiswoode, Ballantyne, London. 17 pp.
- Pennell, Joseph. "Joseph Pannell's Pictures of War Work in England. A Selection from a Series of the Munition Works Made by Him with the Permission and Authority of the British Government." Heinemann, London, 1917, 31 Plates. (Box 9)
- Perris, H.S. "Letter..." London, December, 1914. 2 pp. (Box 9)
- "Plain Speaking. Republic of Portugal. Reasons for the Military Intervention of Portugal in the European War." Abridged from a report published in the Diario do Governo. No. 9 Series 1, of the 17th Janurary, 1917. Eyre & Spottiswoode, London, 1917,27 pp. (Box 9)
- "Poland Under the Germans." Sir Joseph Causton. London, 1916, 30 pp. (Box 9)
- "Poland Under the Germans." The Complete Press, London, 1917, 44 pp. (Box 9)
- Pollock, Frederick (Sir). "The League of Nations and the Coming Rule of Law." Oxford University Press, London, 1918, 15 pp. (Box 9)
- Prince, Morton. "The American Versus the German View of the War." T. Fisher Unwin. London, 1915, 47 pp. (Box 9)
- Puaux, Rene. "The German Colonies. What is to Become of Them?" Wightman, London, 1918, 39 pp. (Box 9)
- Raemaekers, Luis. "Cartoons." National Press Agency, London, 1916. 40 pp. (Text in English and Dutch). (Box 9)
- Raleigh, Walter (Sir). "The War of Ideas. Address... Dec. 12, 1916." Clarendon Press, Oxford, 1917, 24 pp. (Box 9)
- Raede, Arthur. "Russia Under Nicholas II." Thomas Nelson, London, 16 pp. (Box 9)
- "The Reception of Wounded Prisoner Soldiers of Great Britain in Switzerland." Trussoctt, London, 1916, 8 pp. (Box 9)
- Redmond, John E. "Ireland and the War. Speeches...Septemberm 25 th& October 18th, 1914." Reprinted from the Freeman's Journal. 12 pp. (Box 9)
- Redmond, J. E. "The Irish Nation and the War. Extracts from Speeches Made in the House of Commons and in Ireland Since the Outbreak of the War." Sealy, Bryers and Walker, Dublin, 1915. 37 pp. (Box 9)
- Redmond, John E. Speech... 23rd August, 1915. Darling, London, 22 pp. (Box 9)
- Redmond, John. "Strong Words from Mr. Redmond. Treason to the Home Rule Cause." Causton, London, 1916, 6 pp. (Box 9)
- Redmond, John. "The Voice of Ireland... An Interview... and Some Messages from the Representative Irishmen Regarding the Sinn Fein Rebellion." April, 1916. Thomas Nelson, London, 55 pp. (Box 9)
- "Reports on British Prison Camps in India and Burma. Visited by the International Red Cross Committee in Feburary, March, and April, 1917." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 64 pp. (Box 9)
- "Reprisals Against Prisoners of War. Correspondence Between the International Red Cross Committee and the British Government." Sir Joseph Causton, London, 1916, 12 pp. (Box 9)
- Revelstoke, Lord. "British Staying Power. Lord Revelstoke Views Anglo-American Sympathies. Interview Given to the United Press of America." Causton, London, 1916, 8 pp. (Box 9)
- Rimbaud, Isabelle. "In the Whirlpool of War." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1918, 256 p. (Box 16)
- Robertson, J. M. "Britain Versus Germany." T. Fisher Unwin, London. 1917. 124 p. (Box 10)
- Robertson, J. M. "Neutrals and the War. An Open Letter to Heer L. Simons." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1917, 32 pp. (Box 10)
- Robinson, H. Perry. "The Turning Point." Heineman, London, 1917, 290 pp. (Box 17)
- Roesemeier, Hermann. "A German to Germans. An Open Letter." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 42 p. (Box 10)
- Roger, Nooelle. "The Victim's Return." Constable, London, 1917, 134 pp. (Box 10)
- Rose, J. Holland. "Why We Carry On." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1918, 38 pp. (Box 10)
- Ruffin, Henry, and Andre Tudesq. "Brother Tommy." T. Fisher Unwin, London. 1918, 160 pp. (Box 10)
- Ruffin, Henry and Andre Tudesq. "The Square Jaw." Thomas Nelson, London, 103 pp. (Box 10)
- "Russia and Her Allies. Extract from the Verbatim Report of the Imperial Duma, IVth Session. 16th Sitting." Burrup, Mathieson & Sprague, London, 1917, 20 pp. (Box 10)
- Sabatier, Paul. "The Ideals of France... Letter." Reprinted from The Times, Jan. 22, 1915. Unwin Bros., London, 8 pp. (Box 10)
- Salandra, Antonio. "Speech of His Excellency Signor Antonio Salandra in the Capitol of Rome, June 2, 1915, In Reply to the Emperor of Austria and the German Chancellor." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1915, 32 pp. (Box 10)
- Samuel, Herbert. "The War and Liberty." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 128 p. (Box 10)
- Sanday, W. "When Should the War End?" War Time Papers. Evangelical Information Committee. Menpes, London, 1917, 12 pp. (Box 10)
- Scholedield, G. H. "New Zealand, International Information Series, British Empire Section. Vol IV. George Allen & Unwin, London, 1917, 64 pp. (Box 10)
- Schuster, A, and Shipley, A. E. "Britain's Heritage of Science." Constable, London, 1917, 334 pp. (Box 16)
- Scott, Leslie. and Alexander Shaw. "Great Britain and Neutral Commerce." Darling, London, 1915, 17 pp. (Box 10)
- "Security for Allied Loans." 2 pp. Eyre & Spottiswoode, London. (Box 10)
- Selbie, W. B. "Christian Nationalism." War Time Papers, Evangelical Information Committee. Menpes, London, 8 pp. (Box 10)
- "The Sentinel of the Seas. The Tireless Vigil of the British Navy." Harrison, jehring, London, 32 pp. Pictorial. (Box 10)
- Shakespeare, J. H. "The Two Republics." War Time Papers. Evangelical Information Committee. 12 pp. (Box 10)
- "The Sinking of the Lusitania. A German Naval Victory." 1 pp. (Box 10)
- "Slavery in Europe. A letter to Neutral Governments from the Anti-Slavery Society." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 8 pp. (Box 10)
- "The Slavs Among the Nations." Reprinted from La Nation Tcheque of 15th March, 1916. Czech National Alliance in Great Britain. 38 pp. (Box 10)
- Sloss, Robert. "An American's View of the British Mail Censorship." W. Speaight & Sons, London, 1916, 32 pp. (Box 10)
- Sloss, Robert. "Some Facts About India. Interviews with Lord Islington During November, 1916." Burrup, Mathieson & Sprague, London, 1917, 19 pp. (Box 10)
- Smith, George Adam (Sir). "Syria and the Holy Land." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1918, 56 p and maps. (Box 10)
- Smuts, J. C. "War Time Speeches." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 127 p. (Box 10)
- "A South American Priest in Belgium." Darling, London, 1915, 14 pp. (Box 11)
- "A Souviner for Visitors to the British Front." R. Clay, London, 40 pp. (Box 11)
- Spielmann, Isidore (Sir). "The Germans as Others See Them. An Open Letter to Herr Maximilian Harden." W. Speaight, London, August, 1917, 20 pp. (Box 11)
- Sprigg, W. Stanhope. "The British Blockade. What It Means; How It Works." Printed from Pearson's Magazine. George Binny Dibblee, London, 10 pp. (Box 11)
- Stalker, James. "The Luther Celebrations, 1517, 1917." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 21 pp. (Box 11)
- Stanley, Arthur. "Mercy-Workers of the War. An Interview." Causton, London, 1916, 21 pp. (Box 11)
- "The Story of a Sea Flight Told in Official Statements." R. Clay, London, 4 pp. (Box 11)
- "The Straight Path and the Crooked." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 12 pp. (Box 11)
- Strang, Herbert. "Great Britain and the War. A Book for Boys and Girls." Frowde and Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1916, 26 pp. (Box 11)
- Strang, Herbert. "Great Britain and the War. A Book for Boys and Girls." New and Revised Edition. Henry Frowde and Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1918, 45 pp. (Box 11)
- Struycken, A. A. H. "The German Hite Book on the War in Belgium." Commentary. Thomas Nelson. London, 1915, 56 p. (Box 11)
- "Subject Nationalisties of the German Alliance. With Map Drawn from German Sources." Cassell, London, 1917, 4 pp & map. (Box 11)
- "A Suspect Manifesto and a Neutral Expert." 5 pp. (Box 11)
- Suter-Lerch, H. J. "Germany Her Own Judge." George Allen & Unwin. London, 1918, 128 p. (Box 11)
- Swinton, E. D. "The 'Tanks'"(By Request and with Permission.) Reprinted from Strand Magazine. 23 pp. Avenue Press, London. (Box 11)
- "Syria during March 1916. Her Miseries and Disasters. A Series of Articles Published in the Arabic Journal of 'mokattam, of Cairo, on the 30th of March, and 1st April, 1916." Causton, London, 1916. 24 pp. (Box 11)
- "The Third Great War Number of the Fleet Annual and Naval Year Book." (See under "Fleet Annual...") (Box 11, Box 17)
- "Those 'Gentlemen' of Germany." Field & Queen, London, 4vpp. (Box 11)
- "Through Swamp and Forest. The British Campaign in Africa." Harrison, Jehring, London, 32 pp. Pictorial. (Box 11)
- "To Belgium." W. Speaight, London, 1916, 41 pp. (Box 11)
- "To Make Men Traitors. Germany's Attempts to Seduce her Prisoners-of-War." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1918, 26 pp. (Box 11)
- "To our Colleagues in Russia." 3 pp. (Box 11)
- Tolkowsky, S. "The Jewish Colonisation in Palestine." Zionist Organization, London, 1918, 10 pp. (Box 11)
- Toynbee, Arnold J. "The Murderoustyranny of the Turks." Hodder &Stoughton, London, 1917, 35 pp. With preface by Viscount Bryce. (Box 11)
- "The Trail of Barbarians." The Beacon, No. 2. 4 pp. (Box 11)
- "The Treatment of Armenians in the Ottoman Empire. Documents Presented to Viscount Grey of Fallodon... with Preface of Viscount Bryce." Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1916, 684 pp. (Box 17)
- Turczynowicz, Laura de. "When the Prussians Came to Poland." Putman, New York, 1916, 281 p. (Box 16)
- "Turkey: A Past and A Future." Reprinted from the Round Table, for June, 1917. Hodder & Stoughton, London, 1917, 79 pp. (Box 11)
- "Turkish Prisoners In Egypt. A Report by the Delegates of the International Committee of the Red Cross, Extracted and Translated From the Official Reports of the Red Cross Society." London, 1917, 64 pp. (Box 11)
- Union Sacree. "Great Britain in War Time. A Message From His Eminence Cardinal Bourne." Burns & Oates, London, 6 pp. (Box 11)
- Vallotton, Banjamin. "In the Land of Death." Cassell, London, 1917, 35 pp. (Box 11)
- Van der Essen, Leon. "A Short Account of the German Invasion and Occupation of Belgium." T. Fisher Unwin, London, 1918, 104 p. (Box 11)